(Penny:)- Mom still here?
- Yep.
(Penny:)Come on in.
(Penny:)She's not gonna come here
looking for you, is she?
(Leonard:)Oh, relax. She took Sheldon to the hospital
to get a brain scan.
- Oh, my God. What happened?
- Nothing.
(Leonard:)Mother likes looking at brains
and Sheldon likes getting his brain scanned.
Jeez, what a fun couple.
Ugh. She's only here a day and a half...
(Leonard:)...and I'm seriously considering alcoholism
as a new career path.
(Penny:)I talked to her for five minutes yesterday
and I've been half bombed ever since.
(Leonard:)You can't let her get into your head.
- My head, what about yours?
- It's too late for me.
(Leonard:)My head is her summer house.
(Penny:)She was right, you know.
(Penny:)The locus of my identity
is totally exterior to me.
(Leonard:)Oh, yeah, there she is. Hi, mom.
(Penny:)Do you know where I was all morning?
(Penny:)Auditioning with 50 other blondes
for some stupid antidepressant commercial.
(Penny:)And for what?
So I'll finally get my daddy's approval?